friendplay.com 2012-04-18

# Friendplay United States - United States Mobile Friendship, Free SMS, Blogs, Video, Music, Dating, Match Making, and Mobile Phone Community!

Privacy Policy

This policy is effective as of August 8, 2008. 

About Friendplay and the Information We Gather

 **Profile Information submitted by Members to Friendplay**  
Friendplay is an online social networking community that connects people through networks of friends for communicating, sharing and making new friends. To accomplish this, each Member creates his or her own profile, which contains the personal information that the Member chooses to include. This personal information includes such things as:  
    1\. First name or first and last names of the Member (depending on the options selected by the Member),  
    2\. Gender, age, martial status and other, similar personal information,  
    3\. Occupation,  
    4\. Schools attended or companies with whom the Member is associated,  
    5\. Location (e.g., city and state), and  
    6\. Photos, videos or other shared content uploaded by the Member to his or her profile, to the extent that includes personal information. 

**Information Not Directly Submitted by Members or Other Website Users to Friendplay.**  
We also collect some information from Members, as well as from other visitors to our Website, that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type an IP address. This information is gathered from all Members and visitors to the website.  
Display of Members' Information  
Except where a Member might choose to include a full name in his or her profile, a Member's email address and full name will only be used in the following circumstances:  
    1\. When the Member invites a friend via email to become a Friendplay member,  
    2\. When the Member sends a request to another Member to add the other Member to his or her friend list,  
    3\. When we send notifications to the Member relating to his or her use of the Friendplay service or Friendplay Website and,  
    4\. If the Member so chooses, when we send regular notifications, updates, or other news regarding the Friendplay vice or the Friendplay Website.  
Except when inviting or adding friends or as otherwise expressly set forth herein, a Member's email address will never be shared with or displayed to any other person. Members and their friends, and other Members within the network communicate on Friendplay with each other trough the Friendplay service without disclosing email addresses.

 **Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks**  
Except as explained herein, or where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your Membership. However, Friendplay may share profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner with advertisers and other third parties in order to present to Members and other users of the Friendplay Website more targeted advertising, products and services; provided that, in such situations, we will never disclose information that would personally identify you. As set forth above, Friendplay may (i) use your email address to conduct market research for Friendplay’s internal use only; and/or (ii) use your email address to market Friendplay to you (e.g., new features and applications, announcements, opportunities of interest). Friendplay may contact with a third party to conduct such research and marketing; provided that such third party will be fully bound by an obligation of confidentiality to Friendplay and may not use any personally-identifiable information provided by Friendplay other than expressly as instructed by Friendplay and in strict compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

 **Links**  
Friendplay Website contains links to other websites which includes links that are placed there by Friendplay such as in advertisements), as well as by other Friendplay Members. Please be aware that Friendplay is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage all Members and other users of the Friendplay Website to be aware of when they leave our website, and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by Friendplay through the Website.

 **Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are small bits of information that is stored on your computer. We use cookies to identify your Internet browser, store Users’ preferences, and determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on the Friendplay Services. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services.  
Third party advertisements displayed on Friendplay may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers (known as “third party cookies”). Friendplay does not control these third party cookies and Users of the Friendplay Services should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. A pixel tag is a tiny image inserted in a webpage and used to record the number and types of views for that page. We may allow third party pixel tags to be present on Friendplay for purposes of advertising, providing services or data and statistics collection.   
You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on the Friendplay Services.

**Changes in Our Friendplay Privacy Policy**  
If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Website so that Members and other users of Friendplay are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use Members' or other users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify those Members and users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

 **Invite Friend**  
The Friendplay account of every Member is password-protected. We take every precaution to protect the information of the Members, as well as information collected from other users of the Friendplay Website. We use industry standard measures to protect all information that is stored on our servers and within our database. We limit the access to this information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us.

 **Email Choice/Opt-out**  
Members who no longer wish to receive our weekly email updates or other email notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the applicable email or by logging-in and changing their settings in the "Account Settings" section of the Friendplay Website. You can access this page by clicking on the "Profile” –Account Setting link on the top left bar of your Friendplay homepage.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
Ads which appear on this Website are delivered to Members by our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may use cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Friendplay does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed on the computer of any Member or other user of the Friendplay Website by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.

 **Contacting Friendplay**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, Friendplay’s Privacy Practices, please don’t hesitate to Contact Us.
